trendir.com 2017-12-28

# Privacy Policy - Trendir

At [www.trendir.com](htt://www.trendir.com), the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information that is received by Trendir.com and how it is used.

### Log Files

Like many other Web sites, [Trendir.com](https://www.trendir.com/) makes use of log files. These files merely logs visitors to the site – usually a standard procedure for hosting companies and a part of hosting services’s analytics. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. This information is used to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

### Cookies and Web Beacons

[Trendir.com](https://www.trendir.com/) uses cookies to store information about visitors’ preferences, to record user-specific information on which pages the site visitor accesses or visits, and to personalize or customize our web page content based upon visitors’ browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

### DoubleClick DART Cookie

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on [Trendir.com](https://www.trendir.com/).
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our site’s visitors based upon their visit to [Trendir.com](https://www.trendir.com/) and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on Trendir.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-partyad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

### Consent

By using our website, you hereby consent to our privacy policy and agree to its terms.
